How much of your own life are you willing to risk
Risk is a documentary, crime film directed by Laura Poitras.
Capturing the story of WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange with unprecedented access, director Laura Poitras finds herself caught between the
motives and contradictions of Assange and his inner circle in a documentary portrait of power, betrayal, truth and sacrifice.
Self, played by Julian Assange.
Self, played by Sarah Harrison.
Self, played by Jacob Appelbaum.
Self, played by Joseph Farrell.
Self - Lawyer, played by Renata Avila.
Self - Lawyer, played by Jennifer Robinson.
Risk is a 2016 American documentary film written and directed by Laura
Poitras about the WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange.
It was screened in the Directors' Fortnight section at the 2016 Cannes
Film Festival and received generally favorable reviews.
Originally titled "Asylum", the film becomes a journey
into Poitras's disillusionment with Assange.
In the 2016 version of the film, Poitras presents a more
sympathetic position towards Assange.
The 2017 re-cut version focuses more on a critique of Assange as a flawed character, including his alleged
sexual assaults and his "troubling" statements about women and responses to accusations against him.
The film explores themes of asylum, national security agency (nsa),
information leak, investigative journalism, semi-biographical.